Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Records of TWU Local 100 (New York City), 1931-1978.
  - Taxi: Assessment, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Taxi: Clippings, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Taylor Law, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Teamster Organizing, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Teamster Organizing, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Television Program, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Television, undated, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Third Avenue Railway System, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Third Avenue Railway System, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Third Avenue Railway System, 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Third Avenue Railway System, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Third Avenue Railway System, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1952-1954 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Third Avenue Transit Corporation, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Third Ave. Transit Corp: Sections- Correspondence, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Third Ave. Transit Corp: Sections- Correspondence, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Third Ave. Transit Corp: Sections- Membership Lists, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Third Ave. Transit Corp: Sections- Membership Lists, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Third Ave. Transit Corp: Sections: Special Elections, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Third Ave. Transit Corp: Sections: TWU Officers= Meetings, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Towermen's Division, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Towermen's Division, 1958, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Track and Power Distribution Division, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Track and Structure: Asst. Foremen, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Trackmen (I.S.S.), 1940 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Traffic Conference, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Traffic Conferences, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Traffic Problems, 1955-1960 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Train Crews, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Transit, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Transit, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Transit Authority: General I, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Transit Authority: General II, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Transit Authority: General I, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Transit Authority: General II, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Transit Authority: General III, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Transit Authority: General I, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Transit Authority: General II, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1957-1958 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1962-1964 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1968-1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Transit Authority: General, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Transit Authority: Bingham, 1953-1955 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Transit Authority: Budget Data, 1961-1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Transit Authority: Casey, 1953-1955 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Transit Authority: Charity Committee, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Transit Authority: Clerical Force, 1954-1956 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Transit Authority: Clippings, 1946, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Transit Authority: Clippings, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Transit Authority: Daly, 1953-1955 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Transit Authority: Daly, 1956-1957 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Transit Authority: Representation Election, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Transit Authority: Grievance Cases, 1953-1954 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Transit Authority: Grievance Cases, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Transit Authority: Grievance Cases, 1956-1958 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Transit Authority: Inequity Fund, 1960-1961 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Transit Authority: Klein, 1954, 1957-1958 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Transit Authority: Legislation, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Transit Authority: McLernon, 1955-1958 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Transit Authority: McNally, 1951-1955 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Transit Authority: Marschhauser, 1965-1970 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Transit Authority: Minutes, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Transit Authority: Nagelberg, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Transit Authority: O'Grady, 1955-1956, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Transit Authority: Patterson, 1955-1957, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Transit Authority: Representation Election, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Transit Authority: Representation Election, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Representation Election: Special Accounting, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Transit Authority: Station Department, 1954-1956 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Transit Authority: Statistics, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Transit Authority: Step 5 Hearings, 1956-1958 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Transit Authority: Wage Inequity Fund, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Transit Campaign, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Transit Commission Report, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Transit Industry Meeting, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Transit Labor Board, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Transit Labor Conference, Feb 28, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Transit Lines, Sale of (Proposed), 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Transit Mediation Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Transit Police: Organizing, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Transit Record, 1955-1956 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Transit Record, 1970-1973 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Transit Supervisors Organization, 1954-1957 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Transit Supervisors Organization, 1962-1963, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Transit Police, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Transit Truths, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Transportation Benevolent Foundation, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Transportation Employees Industrial Union, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Trial Board, undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Trial Board, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Trial Board I, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Trial Board II, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Trial Board III, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Trial Board, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Trial Board, 1950-1955 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Trial Board, 1952-1953 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Trial Board I, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Trial Board II, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Trial Board: Committee, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Trial Board: 240th St. Barn, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Trial Board: Expulsions, 1954-1955 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Triangle Bus Corp, 1940-1942 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Triboro Bridge and Tunnel Authority, 1949-1951 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Triboro Coach Corp, 1936-1938 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Triboro Coach Corp, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Triboro Coach Corp, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Triboro Coach Corp, 1952-1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - TWU Administrative Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - TWU Express, 1949-1954, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - TWU International Administrative Committee Meeting, 1962-1964 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - TWU Membership Pledge, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - TWU Twentieth Anniversary, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - TWU Twentieth Anniversary: Fund Report, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Unemployment, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Unification: General, 1935-1936 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Unification: General, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Unification: General, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Unification: General, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Unification: General, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Unification: General: I, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Unification: General: II, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Unification: General, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Unification: BMT, 1937-1938 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Unification: BMT, 1939-1941 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Unification: BMT, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Unification: BMT (Hearings Transcript), 1939 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Unification: Campaign for Support I, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Unification: Campaign for Support II, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Unification: Campaign for Support, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Unification: Campaign for Support, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Unification: Campaign for Support I, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Unification: Campaign for Support II, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Unification: Citizen's Transit Committee, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Unification:: Clippings, 1939-1943 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Unification:: Conference, Dec 23, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Unification:: Conference, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Unification:: Conference, 1941-1943 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Unification: Labor's Transit Committee to Support TWU, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Unification: Leaflet Distribution, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Unification: Legislation, undated, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Unification: Madison Square Garden Rally, May 21, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Unification: Madison Square Garden Rally, Feb 9, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Unification: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Unification: Petition before War Board, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Unification: Publicity, 1936-1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Unification: Publicity, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Unification: Press Releases, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Unification: Radio Speeches, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Unification: Reports, 1935-1937 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Unification: Reports, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Unification: Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Unification: Wilkinson Committee, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Uniforms, 1938-1940 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Uniforms: IRT, 1936-1938 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Uniform Conductors Association, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Union Shop Bill, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Union Shop Campaign, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - United Housing Foundation, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - United Housing Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - United Housing Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - United Mine Workers (District 50) NLRB Case, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - United Mine Workers (District 50) NLRB Case, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - United Mine Workers (District 50) NLRB Case, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - United Motormen's Division, 1956-1967 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1937-1939 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1942-1948 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - United Railroad Operating Crafts, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Dept.of Labor, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - United Transit Association, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - United Transit: Employees Council, 1958-1962 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - United Transit: Men's Association, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Urban League, 1953-1956 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Vacations, 1941, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Vacation Camps, 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Vandalism/Assaults, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Vanderbilt, Amy, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Veterans, 1948, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - V J Day, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Wage Adjustments (TWU): Proposed, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Wage Freeze, 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Waldman & Waldman, 1959-1967 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - War Finance Committee, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Watts, Roosevelt, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Weehawken Ferry Protest, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Dances, 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Dance: Souvenir Journal, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Funds, 1953, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Westchester CIO Council, 1954-1956 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Westchester Street Transportation Corp, 1956-1958, 1962-1967 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - West Fordham Transit Co., 1962-1968 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Westinghouse Strike Fund, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - West Side Trade Union Committee, ca.1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - White Plains Bus Co., 1956-1962 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Wicks Bill I, 1939-1943 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Wicks Bill II, 1939-1943 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Wicks Bill III, 1939-1943 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Wilmark Insurance Company, 1950, 1954-1956 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Women Workers, 1941, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Working Agreement, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Working Conditions, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Working Conditions, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Working Conditions: Dispatches, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Workman's Compensation, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Workman's Compensation Board, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Workman's Compensation Cases, 1954-1956 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - World War II: Entry, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Yonkers Bus Co.: General, 1940-1945 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Yonkers Bus Co.: General, 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Yonkers Railroad, 1956-1958 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Yonkers Transit Corp., 1962-1967 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Bargaining, 1937-1939 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Bargaining, 1941-1942 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Bargaining, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Bargaining, 1950-1951 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Bargaining I, 1952-1953 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Bargaining II, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Bargaining I, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Bargaining II, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Bargaining III, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining IV, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining V, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining I, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining II, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining I, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining II, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining I, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining II, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining I, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining II, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining III, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining I, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining II, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining I, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining II, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining III, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Clippings, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: Clippings, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Clippings, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining: Comparative Data, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Comparative Data, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Comparative Data, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Comparative Data, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Congratulations on Contract, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: Disciplinary Bargaining, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining: Injunction, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining: Injunction, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining: Pay Board Decision, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining: Private Bus Lines, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining: Private Bus Lines, 1959-1962 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining: Private Bus Lines, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining: Telegrams, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1947-1948 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Awards I, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Awards II, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Awards, Jun 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Awards, Jul 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration: Avenue B and East Broadway Transit Company, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: Board of Transportation, 1950, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration: Brooklyn Bus Division, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach, 1943 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp. 1-400), 1946 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp. 401-817), 1946 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp. 818-1210), 1946 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp.1-198), 1946 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp. 1-472), 1949 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp. 473-949, i-xiv), 1949 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach (pp. 950-1052), 1949 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach, Nov 1949 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach and Surface Transit, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach and Surface Transit, Jan 1961 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach and Surface Transit, Apr 1961 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration: Fifth Avenue Coach and Surface Transit, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration: Jamaica Buses, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Jul 1945 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Aug 1945 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, May 1946 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, May 1946 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 1-220), 1949 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 221-409), 1949 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 410-639), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 640-814), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 640-814), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 815-996), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 997-1196), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 1197-1429), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 1430-1618), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 1619-1796), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration: New York City Omnibus, Eighth Avenue Coach, Madison Avenue Coach (pp. 1797-1968, i-xx), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Fifth Avenue Coach, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Fifth Avenue Coach, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc., 1941 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc., 1946 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc. (pp. 1-567), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc. (pp. 568-1101), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc. (pp. 1102-1650), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc. (pp. 1651-2192, vi-xvii), 1949 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration: NYC Omnibus Corporation and Madison Avenue Coach, etc. (pp. 2193-2883, xxv), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration: Omnibus Corporation, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 1-131), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 132-282), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 283-449), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 450-595), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 596-836), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 837-998, i-xi), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit, Nov 1949 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 1-230), Nov 1949 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 231-467), Nov 1949 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 468-717), Nov 1949 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 718-1023), Nov 1949 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration: Third Avenue Transit (pp. 1024-1215), Nov 1949 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Arbitrations: Transit Authority, 1953, 1961, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Agreements, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Agreements, 1938 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Agreements, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Agreements, 1940 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Agreements, 1941 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Agreements, 1942 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Agreements, 1943 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Agreements, 1944 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Agreements, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Agreements, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Agreements, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Agreements, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Agreements, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Agreements, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Agreements, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Agreements, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Agreements, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Agreements, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Agreements, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Agreements, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Agreements, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Agreements, 1958-1959 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Agreements, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Agreements, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Agreements, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Agreements, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Agreements, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Agreements, 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Agreements, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Agreements, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 27)